And so, this will be the last event.
Oh!
You did it!
We've been through the Sensitive Championships.
So far
Ayaka has won two in a row.
And to give Mayaka a chance...
We played "Milk, Crisis Milk".
But Ayaka messed up a little, right?
That's when the incident happened.
She gave a hint, a little hint.
You know what happened?
So, all is forgiven!
Yes!
So you didn't just zero Ira out, you zeroed them all out?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
But I'm pretty sure that the sensitive is Ira.
That's the most incorrect information you can give us.
Let's decide on this game.
Whoever wins this game is the most sensitive.
That's too much!
It should be uniform.
Here's the game we're going to play.
8 correct answers in a row!
Nervous breakdown!
8 neurasthenia?
laughs me
♪ It's a now, it's a vow, you and me so lonely
It's a now, it's a vow, you and me so lonely
And now, this will be the last game.Then we'll continue. This will be the last game.
What's the game?
Okay, let's say the title of this game.
"8 Card Nervous Breakdown!
Yay!
We're divided.
If you have to do it in a row...
You have to get it right four times in a row.
In a row.
And each time...
The first one changes.
So if you get one boo-boo...
You mean it resets again?
When you get to the next one.
It's not like you have to remember where you are.
So, the first one to do this gets to go home.
You get to go home!
What?
Really?
You can go home?
You can go home.
Oh, really?
Really?
For real?
All right. - All right.
Okay. Okay.
All right, all right.
Let's do it.
All right. - All right.
Okay, now, I have a card right here.Okay, I have a card here now.
I'm going to turn it over and I'm going to mess it up now.
Go!
Wow!
But I'm going to change the joke I was making earlier.
Be gentle. Nelly's cute.
So let's be nice.
Okay, here we go.
What a mess!
Here we go!
Yes!
Thank you for your hard work!
I can't wait to go home.
Can I have that roll of merry already?
Pappa-pappa!
I got it! I'm almost done with the ironing.
I'm leaving now.
Listen to the guy who thought he was the Joker.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here we go.
Can you do this?
Wow!
Oh, wait.
You mean both times in a row.
I mean, both times in a row, right?This is not impossible.
Are you okay?
Oh, this is not good.
This is not good.
This is bad.
I want to go home!
This is not good.
I wonder if it'll stretch.
Do you want to push it?
I've got about an hour left.
Oh, no, this is bad.
This is bad.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can we try one series and see if we can do it?
Let's change it up.
Let's do one series and reduce it.
Let's reduce it.
Let's change it.
Let's do a series and reduce it by four.
That's right.
But...
Here you go.
Uh...
Uh, this might be difficult.
It's hard
I can't do this at all.
No one ever guesses the first one.
I got an idea.
What is it?
Try one less and you're done.Try one less and you're done.
Ha!
How do you like this turn?
Ehhhh...
Why?
We all agreed.
You've got to concentrate.
You know, just feel it out like you did with the cards.
If you can't, we'll figure it out.
Let's just do this for now.
Let's get our heads in the game.
Let's try our best.
Let's unify the mind one time.
Can we do it?
Yes, sir.
I can do it.
So, please, Kojimon!
I don't want to do it!
Is it black?
Here it is.
Well, well, well.
At first, yes.
If you don't have enough time, it's no good.
It's hard to concentrate at times like that.
That's how it is sometimes.
Bitter and weak.
So you're going to pull the trigger now?So you're saying you're going to pull a "Bitter Weakness" now?
This is the weakest.
The weakest one, but the one you want me to pull.
I'm getting from this one.
Oh!
Here we go.
What?
What the fuck?
I know.
No, this is it.
It's a weakling.
It's a chickenshit.
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
I'm off.
Okay.
What is this, by the way?
A bunny.
Woo hoo!
Se-chan.
Wa-chan!
Oh, wow.
They're all wows.
They're all the same color.
They're all the same.
Next is the camera.
Ka-chan.
Here you go.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey.
He's not dead.He's not dead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're on the right track.
Okay, you pull a snake.
Snake.
Hey, buddy.
That's good.
Iйй.
Well, well, well, well, well.
Are you guys together?
I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you.
Dechavarrian.
That's why Mr. Deshabarian is so strong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yuzu and his kind.
He's a little different from the eyeballs.
Different?
No.
He's got a little bit of an aura about him.
I see it.
Oh, wow!
You've been de-shabelled.
Well done, sir.
Not quite... not quite... not quite... not quite...
There's more to come.
There are three more.
Wait, do you really think I'm writing this?
Wait.
Calm down, calm down, calm down. My mind is racing.
Feel the earth, earth.Feel the earth. Feel the earth.
I can do it. I can do it. I can do it.
I can do it. I can feel the pain and weakness.
I see... I see... He said he's the one.
Here he comes.
Well, well, well. But he was heavy at first.
He's like that. He's a coward.
Is this the second time you've hit him, Mr. Ichikawa?
Impossible! Impossible!
I've been through the whole charade. I can't do it.
I felt it.
We all feel the same way.
We have no pride.
Fans, we would like to cheat and lose one piece.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
But you know, I've been thinking about this for a while now,
I don't get out much every day for a bit.
That's right.
So, I'm going to choose an anime that I think is like this member.
Then, I can pull for Airira, can't I?
I can have such a strong feeling,
So I'm going to choose an anime that I think is like this member.
Enjoy it.
Ending
We have decided on Ms. Ayala!
Then please give it here.
This way, please.
Ah!
Suddenly I thought the flower was one of them.Suddenly I wondered if flowers were one of them.
I wondered if flowers were one of them.
You're going to do it once?
What? Why?
Look at them.
One time... a mimicry...
Just like that.
Monkey.
I'm sure this is the one, like you bought it
You have a lot of these, Hana-chan.
Yes, I do.
Well then, please open it.
This way, please.
There you go!
Wow!
I thought of the picture back there.
When I was arranging this one...
Oh, these are flowers.
He said, "Look at the flowers.
You don't need it to be an image.
That's what I was thinking.
That's what I thought.
It's so unexpected.
Why? Why?
Why?
Oh, my God.
It's huge.
Do you want to see them side by side? Let's do it on your face.
Let's put them side by side. Once on your face.Why don't we line them up? Once in the face.
Did you just say all that?
Okay, then.
I'm glad you said yes.
This is the only one we have. Look at that.
The three of us. Oh, this is the only one.
Right this way.
Wow, it's dense.
It's very dense.
You were here.
Oh, wow.
It's super-neat.
You're very aware of your boss's feelings, aren't you?
You always have Cow's feelings in mind, don't you?
Yeah, we're partners with the bull.
I just slipped.
I really did slip.